练习 1-55：某某先生。有时美国人会出现短暂的思维停顿，
Exercise 1-55, Mr. Thingamajig. Sometimes Americans have little mental pauses, where
某个词就在嘴边，却想不起准确的
something's right on the tip of our tongue, but we can't think of the exact
词；或者我们想用委婉说法替代不雅表达。幸运的是，有一种
word, or when we want to euphemize unseemly speech. Fortunately, there's a
绕开的办法。我们会使用可以代表任何事物的替代词。我
way around that. We use substitution words that can mean anything and everything. I
was rooting willy-nilly through a bunch of stuff, looking every which way for the
dinky little whatchamacallit to fix the gal dong thingamajig but good ol' What's-his
-name and put it in the whoozie-whatsit as usual. Boy oh boy, what a lot of hooey.
Always the same ol' rigamarole with that cockamamie bozo. He's such a pipsqueak. If
I found it, ka-ching, I'd be rich. Which would be just Jim Dandy, I'd be totally
discombobulated. You know who had done you know what with the goofy little gadget
again, so what do you know? There was something rather wrong with it. What a
snafu. I had a heck of a time getting ahold of What's-Her-Name to come over and
take care of it with her special little doohickey that she keeps there in her
thingamabob. For the gazillionth time, the flighty little flibbertigibbet said,
Alrighty! But she wouldn't chilly-shally. She'd schlep over with her widget-fixer
and whatnot to do a bodaciously whiz-bang job on the whole shebang. That's right,
the whole kitten-caboodle no ifs, ands, or buts about it, no malarkey. Okie-dokie,
but she was a skosh busy right then, yadda-yadda-yadda. Yes siree bob, we usually
have gadgets galore, but with the this and that and all the hoopla, it's all topsy
turvy today cause that humongous nincompoop is still in the what's it
acting like everything's just hunky dory. That's a bunch of gobbledygook, pure
gibberish. He's such an old rapscallion. Jiminy Christmas, the shenanigans of that
old fogey, yakety schmackety blah blah blah. Shucks, I just wanted to find it on
my own and not be penalized for it. I'm so darn tired of gimmies and gotchas by a lot
of has-been nosy bones about hobnobbing with hoity-toity wannabes. The real nitty
-gritty is that young and old, they're just a bunch of happy-go-lucky
whippersnappers and cantankerous old fuddy-duddies who don't know diddly. I poked
around the gewgaws, tchotchkes, gimcracks, and knick-knacks, they're in the
doodad. But I found zilch, zero, zippo, nil, nada, and null. So-and-so told me
such-and-such about the diggly-bob, but I just don't know where that is. Sheesh, it's a
big whoop-de-doo when you can't even remember where the gosh-diddly-darned what
-do-you-call-it is.